Retail Store Employees Union Local 345 (Rochester, NY) Records 5823
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Retail Store Employees Union Local 345 (Rochester, NY) Records
1969-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Retail Store Employees Union. Local 345 (Rochester, N.Y.)
5823
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5713171
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 17, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5810: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records 5810 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records on Microfilm 5816 mf: International Bricklayers, Masons, Plasters, Tilelayers and Terrazzo Workers Local 11 (Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5817 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 502 (Canandaigua, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5818 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Local 662 (Mt. Morris, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5819 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1508 (Lyons, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5820 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 240 (East Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5821 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 72 (Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5822 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council, Rochester, NY. Records on Microfilm
Clerks (Retail trade) -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Rochester; Retail Store Employees Union; Retail Store Employees Union. Local 345 (Rochester, N.Y.)
5713171
- New By-Law Committee Minutes (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Local 1602 Syracuse - Official Minutes of Local Union Meetings (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Retail Store Employees Local 345 Union Special Meeting Minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  October 27, 1975
- Special Minutes Local 345 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Executive Board Minutes Beg. 1/70, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- General Membership Meetings (Box 1, Folder 7)
- EB Mtg. Minutes, 1956-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Local 1493 Oswego (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Minutes - Executive Board Meetings (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Local 345 Binder (Box 2, Folder 1)
- A. Philip Randolph Institute (Box 2, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Rochester By-Laws Revision, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO COPE, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- American Way (Box 2, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Conference Long Island (Box 2, Folder 6)
  July 6-8
- Community Services Comm. - AFL-CIO Rochester (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Democratic Party (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Bits and Pieces International - Women's Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Israel Committee (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Israel Dinner - Abe Chatman (Box 2, Folder 11)
- International. Women's Civil Rights Conf., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  September 23-26, 1982
- International. Women's Conference - Washington, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  May 13, 1981
- International Contract Representatives (Box 2, Folder 14)
- International Applications for Employment (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Pregnancy Disability (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Pension Information (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Political Committee - UFCW Local One - Rochester Area (Box 2, Folder 18)
- PAC - Newsletters Local One (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Syracuse COPE Committee (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Resume (J. S. Colombo) (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Merger Notes - Local 345 & Local #1 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Courier Beginning 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Membership - Finances (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Local 345 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Retail Store Employees Union (Box 2, Folder 26)
- By-Laws Revised 1969 & Minutes - Ballots 1970-1972, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Retail Clerks Regional Pension Fund Trust & Amendments (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Retail Clerks Regional Pension Trust Agreement - Plan (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Star Proposals (Box 2, Folder 30)
- News Articles (Box 2, Folder 31)